

PROFILE

I am a software engineer and developer, experienced mainly on Microsoft technologies. Besides the professional experience, I have several research experiences on major branches of Computer Network (mainly software-defined networking).

I love open-source software, and would love to make my tools and utilities publicly available. I've been working on a stable web development methodology and technology, for both large-scale and regular size web applications. That one is closed source.

CONTACT

PHONE: (+98) 918-713-4005

WEBSITE:

https://www.kiarash.pro

EMAIL:

<u>kiarash.s@stu.razi.ac.ir</u> hello@kiarash.pro

HOBBIES

Hiking
Cycling
Book Reading
Swim
Listen to Music

KIARASH SOLEIMANZADEH

CEO/Researcher/Web & Mobile Designer and Developer

EDUCATION

Razi University

2014 - 2018

Master of Information Technology (Multimedia Systems)

Malayer University

2009 - 2014

Bachelor of Software Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pouya Pardaz Karkia Company [CEO]

2014 - 2019

Freelancer [Full Stack Developer]

2005 - Now

PORTFOLIO

Aja University of Medical Science Portal and Sub-Portals

Full Stack Developer (ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework Core, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, ...)

Aja University of Medical Science Professors Comprehensive System

Full Stack Developer (ASP.NET MVC 5, Entity Framework 6, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, ...)

PUBLICATION

SD-WLB: An SDN-aided mechanism for web load balancing based on

server statistics

2019 - Journal Paper

Soleimanzadeh, K., Ahmadi, M., & Nassiri, M. (2019). SD-WLB: An SDN-aided mechanism for web load balancing based on server statistics. ETRI Journal. doi:10.4218/etrij.2018-0188

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Warehouse-Scale Computing (cloud, big data, bioinformatics)

Electronic Commerce

Biomedical Engineering

Database Systems

Multimedia Systems

Software Engineering

Computer Networks

Distributed Systems

SKILLS

- § C#/C/C++/Java/Matlab § Design Patterns § OO Design and Analysis § Software Project Management § DevOps § UML
- 🌎 CSS/HTML 🧠 TypeScript/JavaScript 🥱 C#/VB.NET 🏐 ASP.NET (Inc. ASP.NET Core) 🥞 Microsoft SQL Server 🧐 Angular
- § Microsoft IIS § Docker § Windows Server § Ubuntu/CentOS § MacOS § Git § WebPack/Gulp § MongoDB § Redis
- § Elasticsearch § Sass/Less § Entity Framework (Inc. EF Core) § .NET Framework (Inc. .NET Core)
- SignalR (Inc. Core SignalR) S Xamarin